Guide to the Historic Photograph Subject File circa 19th century-20th century
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 2: Alaska
  - Food cache shed, 1 item (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - College campus - Alaska 1939, 1 item (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Food cache sheds, 1 item (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Dog sled team, 1 item (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Sailboat, 1 item (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Totem poles at Wrangell, AK, 1 item (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Sailing ships in harbor, 1 item (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Fairbanks, AK, June 13, 1905, 1 item (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Sourdough Hotel Ad - Dawson, Yukon Ter., 1900, 1 item (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Mary Avery - table of Alaskan items at WSC lib., 1 item (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Sitka, AK, 3 items (Box 5, Folder 66.1)
  - Skagway, AK, 4 items (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Alaskan Flag, 1 item (Box 5, Folder 67.1)
- Series 3: Bridges and Dams
  - Subseries 3.1: Bridges
    - Milwaukee railroad bridge - Spokane, 10/22/13, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Spokane Falls and bridge 1899, 2 items (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Upper Falls, Spokane River, April 1925, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Various Bridges - Spokane, 4 items (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Lake Washington floating bridge - Seattle, 6 items (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Lake Washington ship canal project - 1914, 3 items (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Dungeness River bridge, October 1934, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - George Washington memorial bridge - Seattle 1935, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Aurora Ave. bridge - Seattle, 1932, 3 items (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Steilacoom lake and bridge - Tacoma, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Tacoma Creek bridge - 1/2 mile upstream from Pend Oreille Highway, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - First Tacoma Narrows bridge "Galloping Gertie" 1940, 2 items (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Tacoma Narrows bridge, 1940's, 3 items (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Vantage bridge, Columbia River, WA, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Old Marcus railroad bridge, Columbia R., 1915, 1 item + 1 negative (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Longview bridge over Columbia R., 2/21/30, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Railroad and highway bridge over Columbia R. Kettle Falls, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Construction of concrete bridge - Colfax, 1915, 56 items (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - O.R. and N. railroad bridge - Colfax, April 1908, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Kelso bridge, WA, 2 items (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Three bridges over Cowlitz R., Kelso, WA, 3 items (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Manning bridge, Whitman Co., 1 item (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Buena bridge - built 1910, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Deception Pass bridge - Whidbey Island, WA, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Omak bridge, 1929, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Pasco, WA "The open draw", c. 1890, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Yakima River bridge - Union Gap, 2 items (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Courtwright bridge, Lewis Co., 2 items (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Rough-hewn timber bridge, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Various Washington bridges, 16 items (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Lawyer Canyon Bridge, 1909, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 30.5)
    - Lewiston-Clarkston bridges, 6 items (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Sandpoint, ID two-mile wooden bridge, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 31.5)
    - Clearwater River bridge at Spaulding, ID, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Northern Pacific Railroad wreck of the "S" bridge, Feb. 11, 1903, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Coos Bay bridge - Oregon Coast Highway, 2 items (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Astoria Bridge, Astoria, Oregon, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 34.1)
    - Crooked River Bridge, Oregon, 2 items (Box 6, Folder 34.2)
    - Yaquina Bay Bridge, Oregon, 2 items (Box 6, Folder 34.3)
    - Umatilla Bridge, Oregon, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 34.4)
    - San Francisco - Oakland Bay Bridge, 2 items (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Douglass Memorial bridge - Redwood Highway, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Reconstruction of Bridge 116 unit #2, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Railroad bridges, 8 items (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Subseries 3.2: Dams
    - Nine Mile Dam, Spokane River, 2 items (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Little Falls on Spokane River, 2 items (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Rock Island Dam and irrigation project; part of the Columbia River Basin project, 74 items (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Grand Coulee Dam, c. 1957, 5 items (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Grand Coulee Dam and vicinity, 23 items (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Grand Coulee Dam site, pre-construction, 10 items (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Grand Coulee Dam - construction, 7 items (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Grand Coulee Dam construction, site and vicinity, 27 items (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Grand Coulee Dam - aerial Photographs, 2 items (Box 6, Folder 46.1)
    - Bonneville Dam on Columbia River, summer 1935, 42 items (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Bonneville Dam, September 1936, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Bonneville Dam construction, Dec. 20, 1934, 1 oversize item (Box 6, Folder 48.1 (o.s.))
    - Little Goose lock and dam - Lower Snake R., 1970, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Gorge Powerhouse - Ross Dam, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Diablo Dam - Skagit River, 9 items (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Cedar Falls Dam, 1903-1905, 4 items (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Chelan power house waterway, 3 items (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Lake Cle Elum dam, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Cushman Dam and power project, 1925-1926, 8 items (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Water conservation dam, Yakima Co. Aug. 12, 1936, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Long Lake Dam construction, 1911-1914, 18 items (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Long Lake Dam and power house, 5 items (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - McNary Dam, 12 items (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Boulder Dam, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Fore Bay Dam, June 13, 1935, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Norris Dam, 1936, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Ballard Locks, 5 items (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - American Falls hydro-electric plant, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Arrow Rock Dam, 2 items (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Gold Springs Dam - Hermiston, OR, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Brownlee Dam, Idaho, 2 items (Box 6, Folder 66.1)
    - Shoshone Dam, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 66.2)
    - Cabinet Gorge Dam, 3 items (Box 6, Folder 66.3)
    - Unidentified dam, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 67)
- Series 4: Columbia River
  - Columbia River Highway, 5 items (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Columbia River Highway. Bardell Fototone Miniatures., 21 images (Box 7, Folder 1.5)
  - Mouth of Columbia R., wreck of SS Iowa, 2 items (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Columbia River bar with sailing vessel, 1 item (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Columbia R. near Bonneville Dam, 2 items (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Columbia R. at Beacon Rock, 2 items (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Celilo Falls, 1952, 1 item (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Bridge of the Gods, Stevenson, WA, 1 item (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Columbia R. clearance project, 1939, 1 item (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Rosa Irrigation system canal, 3 items (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Grand Coulee dam site, Mason City, 1 item (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Columbia River east of Wenatchee, 1 item (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Columbia River, 1 item (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - The Dalles, Columbia River, 2 items (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Celilo Falls, Columbia River, Oregon, 1 item (Box 7, Folder 13.1)
  - Columbia River gorge scenes, 8 items (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Columbia River, Kettle Falls, 2 items (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Columbia River, Kettle Falls, 1 item (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Columbia River, Kettle Falls, 7 items (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Mouth of Columbia River, 1 item (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Cascades of the Columbia River, 2 items (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Rock formation south of Wenatchee, 1 item (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Columbia River, Vantage Ferry, 1 item (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Vista House, Columbia River, Oregon, 1 item (Box 7, Folder 21.1)
  - Multnomah Falls, Columbia River, Oregon, 1 item (Box 7, Folder 21.2)
  - Evergreen Highway, Columbia River, 1 item (Box 7, Folder 21.3)
- Series 5: Cities and Towns
  - Aberdeen Daily, world building, 2 items (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Agate Beach, Oregon, 1 item (Box 7, Folder 22.1)
  - Ainsworth, WA, 1 item (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Almira, WA - school house, 1915, 1 item (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - American Lake - veterans hospital, 7 items (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Anaconda, MT, 1 item (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Ashland, Oregon, 1 item (Box 7, Folder 25.2)
  - Astoria, OR and Anacortes, WA, 2 items (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Baker, OR, 1 item (Box 7, Folder 26.5)
  - Bellingham, WA, 6 items (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Blain, WA - peace arch, 2 items (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Bremerton and Port Orchard, WA, 13 items (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Brewster, WA - saloon, 1900, 1 item (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Burke, WA - cemetery, 1 item (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Butte, Montana, 2 items (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Cashmere, WA, 1 item (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Cathlamet, WA - Hudson's Bay trading post, 1 item (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Cedonia, WA, 3 items (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Centralia, WA, 4 items (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Chehalis, WA, 11 item (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Chehalis, WA - Jackson Prairie courthouse, 5 items (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Chelan, WA, 2 items (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Cheney, WA - various scenes, 9 items (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Chesaw, Washington, 1 item (Box 7, Folder 40.1)
  - Chewelah, WA, 2 items (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Clarkston - postcard, 1910, 1 item (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Cle Elum - Hidden Valley Guest Ranch, 5 items. (Box 7, Folder 42.2)
  - Clinton, British Columbia, Canada, 1 item (Box 7, Folder 42.5)
  - Coeur d'Alene, 4 items (Box 7.5, Folder 43)
  - Colfax - postcards, 13 items (Box 7.5, Folder 44)
  - Colfax - postcards, 16 items (Box 7.5, Folder 45)
  - Colfax flood, 1910, 3 items (Box 7.5, Folder 46)
  - Colfax flood, 1948, 9 items (Box 7.5, Folder 46.5)
  - Colfax - various buildings, 8 items (Box 7.5, Folder 47)
  - Colfax - phone exchanges, 1927-1931, 2 items (Box 7.5, Folder 47.3)
  - Colfax - Bussie Apts fire, ca. 1950, 12 items (Box 7.5, Folder 47.5)
  - Colfax - monuments, 2 items (Box 7.5, Folder 48)
  - Colfax - 1922 photos by Lawrence Shea, 5 items (Box 7.5, Folder 48.5)
  - Colton, WA - St. Gall's Church, 1905; Flood, 1910, 2 items (Box 7.5, Folder 49)
  - Connell, WA, 2 item (Box 7.5, Folder 50)
  - Copalis Beach, WA, 2 items (Box 7.5, Folder 51)
  - Corvallis, OR - Oregon State College, 2 items (Box 7.5, Folder 52)
  - Cottonwood, ID - hotel, 1 item (Box 7.5, Folder 53)
  - Cottonwood, Idaho - St. Gertrude's Convent, 1 item (Box 7.5, Folder 53.1)
  - Coupeville, WA, 2 items (Box 7.5, Folder 54)
  - Coveland, WA - Whidbey Island, 1937, 1 item (Box 7.5, Folder 55)
  - Crescent City/Pebble Beach, CA, 1 item (Box 7.5, Folder 55.1)
  - Crescent City, Canada, 2 items (Box 7.5, Folder 55.2)
  - Creston, WA, 1 item (Box 7.5, Folder 56)
  - The Dalles, OR, 1858, 1865, 1908 and Dallesport, WA, ca. 1964, 7 items (Box 7.5, Folder 57)
  - Dawson, Yukon Territory, Canada, 1900, 3 items (Box 7.5, Folder 58)
  - Dawson Creek, British Columbia, Canada, 1 item (Box 7.5, Folder 58.1)
  - Dawson City, Canada, 1 item (Box 7.5, Folder 58.2)
  - Dayton, WA, 6 items (Box 7.5, Folder 59)
  - Davenport, WA, 1 item (Box 7.5, Folder 60)
  - Dunsmuir, CA, 21 item (Box 7.5, Folder 61)
  - Edmonds, WA, 15 items (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Edwall, WA, 4 items (Box 8, Folder 1.5)
  - Elk City, ID, 2 items (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Elk River, ID, 1 item (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Ellensburg, WA, 3 items (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Endicott, WA, 3 items (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Everett, WA, 9 items (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Ewan, WA, 1 item (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Farmington - monument, 2 items (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Flora, OR, 5 items (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Fort Lewis, WA, June 1, 1937, 1 item (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Freeport, WA, 1873, 2 items (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Friday Harbor, 1 item (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Garfield, WA, including a 2002 State National Bank Calendar with historical photographs, 3 items (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Gilmore, ID, 3 items (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Goldendale, WA, 7 items (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Grangeville, 3 items (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Grays Harbor, 4 items (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Haines Junction, Canada, 1 item (Box 8, Folder 17.1)
  - Hanford, c. 1925 and Seattle First National Bank Payroll 1940s, 19 items (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Helena, Montana - Buildings, 2 items (Box 8, Folder 18.1)
  - Hoquiam, WA - library, 1 item (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Hunters, WA, 3 items (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Indian, WA, 1 item (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Interior, WA, 1940, 1 item (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Ione, WA - parade, 1915, 5 items (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - John Day, Oregon, 1 item (Box 8, Folder 23.1)
  - Johnson, WA, 6 items (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Joseph, Oregon, 1 item (Box 8, Folder 24.1)
  - Kalispell, MT, 1 item (Box 8, Folder 24.3)
  - Kaslo, British Columbia, Canada, 1 item (Box 8, Folder 24.5)
  - Kelso, WA, 3 items (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Kendrick, ID, 3 items (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Kennewick, WA, 4 items (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Ketchum, Idaho, 2 items (Box 8, Folder 27.1)
  - Kettle Falls St. Paul's Mission, 3 items (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Kuna, ID - September 1908, first school, 1 item (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Lacey, WA - St. Martin's College, 1 item (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - La Crosse, WA, 1 item (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - La Grande, OR - Moose Lodge, 1 item (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Lakewood, WA - community center, 1 item (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - La Push, WA, 7 items (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Lapwai, ID, 1 item (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Lewiston, ID and Clarkston, WA, 29 items (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Lewiston, ID, ca. 1922, 28 items (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Lewis, Co., WA, 2 items (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Lind, WA - 1902, 1 item (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Long Beach, CA - earthquake, March 10, 1933, 8 items (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Longview, WA, 17 items (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Maryhill Museum of Fine Arts, Maryhill, WA, 22 items (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Mason Co., June 7, 1937, 1 item (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Medical Lake, hospital, c. 1900, 1 item (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Missoula, MT, 3 items (Box 8, Folder 43.5)
  - Monroe, WA, 1 item (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Montesano, WA, 2 items (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Swiss Motel, Montpelier, Idaho, 1 item (Box 8, Folder 45.1)
  - Moscow, ID, 4 items (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Moscow, ID 1922 by Lawrence Shea, 2 items (Box 8, Folder 46.1)
  - Moscow, ID University of Idaho 1922 by Lawrence Shea, 5 items (Box 8, Folder 46.5)
  - Moses Lake, WA, 1968, 3 items (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Mossy Rock, WA - school, 1 item (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Mullan, ID, 4 items (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Nampa, Idaho - Oregon Short Line Depot, 1 item (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Nelson, BC, 2 items (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Netarts, Oregon, 1 item (Box 8.5, Folder 1)
  - Newhalem, WA, 4 items (Box 8.5, Folder 2)
  - Newport, OR, 1 item (Box 8.5, Folder 3)
  - Newport, WA, 5 items (Box 8.5, Folder 4)
  - North Yakima, WA, 4 items (Box 8.5, Folder 5)
  - Oakesdale, WA, c.1915, 1 item (Box 8.5, Folder 6)
  - Ocean Park, WA, c.1937, 3 items (Box 8.5, Folder 7)
  - Okanagan, WA - hotel, 1 item (Box 8.5, Folder 8)
  - Okanagan Lake, British Columbia, Canada, 1 item (Box 8.5, Folder 9)
  - Olympia, WA - Capital Grounds, 5 items (Box 8.5, Folder 10)
  - Olympia, WA, 8 items (Box 8.5, Folder 11)
  - Olympia, WA - Olympia High School, 1907-1909, 9 items (Box 8.5, Folder 12)
  - Olympia, WA - 1905 state legislative session, 1 item (Box 8.5, Folder 13)
  - Olympia, WA - legislative and capitol building, 11 item (Box 8.5, Folder 14)
  - Olympia, WA - state legislature, 19 items (Box 8.5, Folder 15)
  - Omak, WA, 13 items (Box 8.5, Folder 16)
  - Oregon City, Oregon - McLoughlin House, 8 items (Box 8.5, Folder 17)
  - Orofino, ID, 1 item (Box 8.5, Folder 18)
  - Packwood, WA, 1 item (Box 8.5, Folder 19)
  - Palouse, WA, 2 items (Box 8.5, Folder 20)
  - Palouse, WA, 7 items (Box 8.5, Folder 21)
  - Palouse High School, 15 items (Box 8.5, Folder 22)
  - Pasco, WA, 4 items (Box 8.5, Folder 23)
  - Pe Ell, WA, 1 item (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Pendleton, Oregon, 1 item (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Penticton, British Columbia, 1921, 1 item (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Peshastin, WA, 15 items (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Port Angeles, WA, 15 items (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Port Angeles - original town layout, 1 item (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Port Blakely - water front, 1 item (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Port Townshend, WA, 2 items (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Portland, OR - Trinity Episcopal church, 1 item (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Portland - Lewis and Clark College, 3 items (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Portland, OR - Miscellaneous, 34 items (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Prince Rupert, Canada, 1 item (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Promontory Summit, UT - May 10, 1869, 1 item (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Pullman - Main Street, c. 1912, 1 item (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Pullman - Zender Bros. Blacksmith Shop, 1 item (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Pullman - City Hall, built 1892, 1 item (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Pullman - Flood of March, 1910, 18 items (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Pullman - Flood of March, 1910, 22 items (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Pullman - Pioneer Parade, c.1920, 1 item (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Pullman - postcards, 9 items (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Pullman - Main Street, c.1905, 1 item (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Pullman - parades, 7 items (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Pullman - photos taken from Slagle papers, 11 item (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Pullman - misc. town photos, 20 items (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Downtown Pullman, c.1920, 1 item (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Pullman, 1891 - McConnell Chambers Dry Goods Store, First National Bank, town panorama, 3 items (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Pullman - 1972 flood, 14 items (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Pullman - Jan. 13, 1928 flood, 2 items (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Pullman - Northern Pacific depot, 1 item (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Pullman - Armistice Day parade, 1919, 1 item (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Pullman - W.H. Latta and E.W. Downen behind post office, 1 item (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Pullman - White Drug interior, c. 1890, 1 item (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Pullman churches - United Presbyterian, Congregational, and others, 7 items (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Pullman - Christian churches, 4 items (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Pullman - Methodist Episcopal church, 2 items (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Pullman - North Pacific Depot "Cougar Special" September 16, 1940, 1 item (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Pullman - North Pacific Depot, c. 1920, 3 items (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Pullman - crowded train station, Feb. 1912, 1 item (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Pullman - Main St. and the Washington Hotel, 13 items (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Pullman - Ried Residence, Main St., 1 item (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Pullman - Lewiston Stage, 1890, 2 items (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Pullman - Culuh, Drucker, and Steel Residences, 1931, 1 item (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Pullman - Old National Bank, interior, 1 item (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Pullman - train depot, 1934, 5 items (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Pullman - 1950's downtown, 4 items (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Pullman - Klemgard residence, January, 1909, 2 items (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Pullman - baseball teams, 1891, 1 item (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Pullman - John Matthews, attorney, 1910, 1 item (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Pullman - Neill Public Library and Pullman Community Cultural Center planning slides, 1980s, 39 items (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Pullman - Post Office (negative), 1 item (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Pullman - Post Office construction, 1931, 25 items (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Pullman - Seattle First National Bank opening day, c. 1948, 4 items (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Pullman - Seattle First National Bank, 1950, 1 item (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Pullman - Emerson Mercantile Co., 1912, 1 item (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Pullman - Hotel Pullman, 1897, 1 item (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Pullman - WSC auction, 1 item (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Pullman - Pullman Eng. Co., 1921, 1 item (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Pullman - floods, 1947 and 1948, 30 items (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Pullman - Professional Mall, 1972, 3 items (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Pullman - Seattle First National Bank employees, 6 items (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Pullman - airport, 2 items (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Pullman - WSC, winter, 1910, 1 item (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Pullman - Artesian Hotel, 1910, 1 item (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Pullman - Viaduct construction, 1938; R.R. bridge, 1910, 3 items (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Pullman - North Pacific Railway, June 9, 1959, 5 items (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Pullman - area view, 1921, 2 items (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Pullman - Armistice Day Parade, 11/11/18, 2 items (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Pullman - Residential Homes, 8 items (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Pullman - after cyclone, July 13, 1920, 7 items (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - empty - dispersed to other folders (MOE, 10/2008), 0 items (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Pullman - WWI trainees leaving 8/12/18, 6 items (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Pullman - Kiwanis 1927 hotel design competition, 7 items (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Pullman - Artesian Well, 1913, 2 items (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Pullman - Willow Brook Farm, 1918, 3 items (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Pullman - Union Pacific Depot, c. 1930's, 2 items (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Pullman - pre-1900, 24 items (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Pullman - pre-1920, 9 items (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Pullman - pre-1950, 10 items (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Pullman - post-1950, 4 items (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Pullman -rural photos, 8 items (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Pullman - Flood of March, 1910, 42 items (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Pullman - school dedication, Oct. 21, 1892, 2 items (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Puyallup - Ezra Meeker statue, 1 item (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Quebec, Canada, 10 items (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Reardon, WA, May, 1915, 1 item (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Republic, WA - mining town, 2 items (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Richland, WA, 13 items (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Rocke Harbor - San Juan Islands, 7 items (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Roslyn, WA, 2 items (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - St. John, WA, 8 items (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - St. Maries, ID, 4 items (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - St. Mary's Mission, WA 1913, 3 items (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Salem, Oregon - Capital Building, 1 item (Box 10, Folder 43.1)
  - Sandon, B.C. - preparing for horse race, December 25, 1896, 1 item (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Sandpoint, ID, 1 item (Box 10, Folder 44.5)
  - Sawyer cabin, WA, 1 item (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Sequim, WA - Olympic Hwy, Oct. 29, 1934, 1 item (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Seattle - greatest snowstorm - Jan. 1916, 1 item (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Seattle - prisoner execution - Jan. 18, 1882, 1 item (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Seattle - photos of the Great Fire of June, 1889, 8 items (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Seattle - area views, c.1890's, 2 items (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Seattle - aerial views, 5 items (Box 10, Folder 50.1)
  - Seattle - various landmark buildings, 10 items (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Seattle - various, 11 item (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Seattle - Seattle Boat Parade, 1 item (Box 10, Folder 52.1)
  - Robinson's Drug Store, 1 item (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Seattle - Financial district - lower 2nd Ave., 3 items (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Seattle - hotels - Washington, Olympic, Dunbar, and Edmond Meany, 9 items (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Seattle - Old City Hall, c. 1903, 2 items (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Seattle - Seattle Federal Building, 1 item (Box 10, Folder 56.1)
  - Seattle - Cornish school, 1 item (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Seattle - First Railroad station, 2 items (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Seattle - public library, June 18, 1937, 1 item (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Seattle - Seattle Public Library, 1 item (Box 10, Folder 59.1)
  - Seattle - YWCA for black women, 1 item (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Seattle - hospitals, 3 items (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Seattle - Pike Place Market, June, 1937, 3 items (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Seattle - Monorail, 1 item (Box 11, Folder 2.1)
  - Seattle - street scenes - 2nd northward, 2 items (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Seattle - street scenes, 5 items (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Seattle - street scenes - 2nd Ave, 3rd Ave, Pike Street, Business District, 9 items (Box 11, Folder 5)